

CONTACT ME AT

- Minsk, Belarus
- (**t**) +375 (29) 703 14 77
- artsemyakautsou@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/artsemyakautsou/

SKILLS

- (HTML5
- (S) CSS3
- ✓ JavaScript (≥ES6), PHP
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Scss
- Responsive design (desktop, tablet, mobile)
- **⊘** Git
- Cross browser compatible websites
- Bootstrap, Tailwind
- JQuery, React

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- ✓ Visual Studio Code
- Figma, Photoshop
- ✓ CMS: WordPress, Bitrix, ModX
- **⊘** Webpack
- **⊘** MySQL

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate

German Elementary

Russian Advanced

ARTSEM YAKAUTSOU

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

5th September 1989

A web developer with over 2 years experience in frontend and a passion for responsive website design.

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

RS School Courses, from The Rolling Scopes Developer Community

Javascript (≥ES6) | Jan 2021 - Apr 2022

TeachMeSkills Courses

Front-end development | Jun 2020 - Dec 2020

Online youtube Javascript courses (Vladilen Minin)

Javascript (≥ES6), React, SCSS | Sep 2020 - present

Online lessons, webinars HTML Academy

Front-end development | Jun 2020 - present

Online HTML & CSS courses from Anna Blok

HTML, CSS, JQuery | Nov 2020 - Jan 2021

Online courses and webinars from webDev

Front-end development | 2020 - present

WORK EXPERIENCE

Algimed, LLC

Front-end developer | Aug 2021 - present

- Development of front-end projects.
- Adaptive and cross-browser layout, code refactoring.
- User interface development.
- Technical optimization of company sites.

Freelancer

Web developer | Mar 2020 - Aug 2021

- Administration and technical support of sites.
- Technical improvements on sites.
- SEO site optimization.
- Refactoring Javascript.
- Creation of new sections, pages of sites and more.
- Development Single Page Applications (SPA).

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Minsk Innovation University

Master's degree | May 2015 - Jan 2018

Economics and Enterprise Management
Master of Economics and Management